Class name: File

Subclasses: Directory 
Responsibilities: 
* Return the contents of itself
* Return the name of itself
* Return its parent directory
* Set the name of itself
* Set the contents of itself
* Append contents to itself
* Erase contents of itself
* Set its parent directory
* Make a copy of itself and add it to a given directory with a new name

Collaborators:
* Directory
*JShellFileExistsException
* JShellFileExistsException