Class name: GetCommand 
Parent class: JShellCommand 

Responsibilities: 
* check if the arguments of command that the user types is valid or not
* Retrieves the file at an URL and adds it to the current working directory
* Scan the raw html codes in a given URL
* Create a file named with the last segment of URL and the contents set to be the raw html codes.

Collaborators: 
* Directory
* File
* JShellURLInvalidException
* JShellArgsInvalidException